const level11questions = [
   
{
    question: "What is 35 + 40?",
    options: ["69", "75", "89", "36"],
    answer: "75"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 44 + 16?",
    options: ["37", "60", "89", "64"],
    answer: "60"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 55 + 34?",
    options: ["25", "89", "42", "11"],
    answer: "89"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 71 + 11?",
    options: ["43", "91", "82", "60"],
    answer: "82"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 81 + 15?",
    options: ["91", "41", "96", "46"],
    answer: "96"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 43 + 56?",
    options: ["51", "16", "99", "66"],
    answer: "99"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 21 + 51?",
    options: ["42", "52", "35", "72"],
    answer: "72"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 18 + 38?",
    options: ["35", "86", "56", "26"],
    answer: "56"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 19 + 37?",
    options: ["88", "71", "56", "51"],
    answer: "56"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 52 + 29?",
    options: ["36", "27", "72", "81"],
    answer: "81"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 41 + 22?",
    options: ["47", "77", "68", "63"],
    answer: "63"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 58 + 24?",
    options: ["57", "15", "53", "82"],
    answer: "82"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 63 + 22?",
    options: ["64", "26", "85", "49"],
    answer: "85"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 34 + 32?",
    options: ["66", "13", "39", "74"],
    answer: "66"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 82 + 13?",
    options: ["28", "95", "70", "32"],
    answer: "95"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 48 + 41?",
    options: ["70", "66", "10", "89"],
    answer: "89"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 65 + 29?",
    options: ["94", "53", "13", "36"],
    answer: "94"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 42 + 27?",
    options: ["92", "69", "54", "40"],
    answer: "69"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 24 + 12?",
    options: ["58", "54", "42", "36"],
    answer: "36"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 27 + 45?",
    options: ["72", "18", "41", "77"],
    answer: "72"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 33 + 10?",
    options: ["43", "54", "44", "95"],
    answer: "43"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 36 + 51?",
    options: ["17", "93", "77", "87"],
    answer: "87"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 34 + 46?",
    options: ["80", "48", "87", "69"],
    answer: "80"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 45 + 42?",
    options: ["51", "87", "93", "97"],
    answer: "87"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 51 + 25?",
    options: ["26", "29", "33", "76"],
    answer: "76"
  },
  
  {
    question: "What is 24 + 18?",
    options: ["85", "12", "79", "42"],
    answer: "42"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 21 + 61?",
    options: ["60", "75", "55", "82"],
    answer: "82"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 10 + 85?",
    options: ["91", "95", "32", "12"],
    answer: "95"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 66 + 15?",
    options: ["81", "97", "83", "61"],
    answer: "81"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 36 + 17?",
    options: ["13", "90", "52", "53"],
    answer: "53"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 18 + 80?",
    options: ["82", "98", "66", "48"],
    answer: "98"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 65 + 22?",
    options: ["53", "87", "10", "73"],
    answer: "87"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 47 + 17?",
    options: ["11", "64", "21", "10"],
    answer: "64"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 24 + 48?",
    options: ["12", "72", "53", "79"],
    answer: "72"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 18 + 14?",
    options: ["54", "85", "24", "32"],
    answer: "32"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 20 + 18?",
    options: ["93", "71", "54", "38"],
    answer: "38"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 26 + 65?",
    options: ["67", "18", "91", "73"],
    answer: "91"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 22 + 62?",
    options: ["84", "76", "36", "81"],
    answer: "84"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 59 + 23?",
    options: ["82", "65", "32", "98"],
    answer: "82"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 69 + 13?",
    options: ["21", "82", "78", "57"],
    answer: "82"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 27 + 19?",
    options: ["49", "39", "46", "50"],
    answer: "46"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 60 + 19?",
    options: ["57", "22", "79", "80"],
    answer: "79"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 35 + 57?",
    options: ["92", "10", "26", "61"],
    answer: "92"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 17 + 23?",
    options: ["13", "31", "49", "40"],
    answer: "40"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 45 + 30?",
    options: ["75", "35", "81", "10"],
    answer: "75"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 47 + 41?",
    options: ["88", "19", "87", "64"],
    answer: "88"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 29 + 14?",
    options: ["79", "50", "83", "43"],
    answer: "43"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 20 + 42?",
    options: ["32", "96", "62", "93"],
    answer: "62"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 50 + 25?",
    options: ["45", "24", "75", "60"],
    answer: "75"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 18 + 64?",
    options: ["84", "71", "95", "82"],
    answer: "82"
  },
  
  {
    question: "What is 39 + 58?",
    options: ["98", "37", "27", "97"],
    answer: "97"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 22 + 25?",
    options: ["94", "76", "47", "22"],
    answer: "47"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 58 + 14?",
    options: ["72", "91", "18", "21"],
    answer: "72"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 22 + 54?",
    options: ["76", "46", "35", "49"],
    answer: "76"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 44 + 45?",
    options: ["80", "89", "99", "71"],
    answer: "89"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 10 + 84?",
    options: ["78", "59", "63", "94"],
    answer: "94"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 65 + 13?",
    options: ["70", "19", "42", "78"],
    answer: "78"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 29 + 24?",
    options: ["53", "93", "32", "39"],
    answer: "53"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 39 + 13?",
    options: ["95", "52", "36", "21"],
    answer: "52"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 55 + 25?",
    options: ["83", "17", "87", "80"],
    answer: "80"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 37 + 15?",
    options: ["52", "85", "95", "24"],
    answer: "52"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 42 + 39?",
    options: ["98", "54", "23", "81"],
    answer: "81"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 14 + 45?",
    options: ["90", "10", "48", "59"],
    answer: "59"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 23 + 73?",
    options: ["93", "25", "96", "20"],
    answer: "96"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 62 + 33?",
    options: ["36", "17", "95", "35"],
    answer: "95"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 42 + 45?",
    options: ["32", "77", "87", "90"],
    answer: "87"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 44 + 39?",
    options: ["69", "64", "12", "83"],
    answer: "83"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 36 + 15?",
    options: ["70", "78", "97", "51"],
    answer: "51"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 14 + 52?",
    options: ["66", "20", "27", "67"],
    answer: "66"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 40 + 59?",
    options: ["43", "99", "41", "78"],
    answer: "99"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 25 + 44?",
    options: ["69", "63", "54", "75"],
    answer: "69"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 16 + 22?",
    options: ["40", "17", "38", "99"],
    answer: "38"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 14 + 58?",
    options: ["41", "72", "53", "83"],
    answer: "72"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 10 + 67?",
    options: ["88", "77", "61", "34"],
    answer: "77"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 53 + 40?",
    options: ["92", "47", "93", "57"],
    answer: "93"
  },
  
  {
    question: "What is 62 + 32?",
    options: ["94", "13", "60", "19"],
    answer: "94"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 25 + 55?",
    options: ["68", "98", "90", "80"],
    answer: "80"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 29 + 61?",
    options: ["40", "25", "90", "28"],
    answer: "90"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 32 + 11?",
    options: ["81", "79", "80", "43"],
    answer: "43"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 83 + 13?",
    options: ["68", "46", "96", "82"],
    answer: "96"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 30 + 25?",
    options: ["55", "93", "94", "77"],
    answer: "55"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 24 + 38?",
    options: ["54", "98", "62", "81"],
    answer: "62"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 41 + 37?",
    options: ["78", "25", "91", "35"],
    answer: "78"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 21 + 44?",
    options: ["25", "67", "37", "65"],
    answer: "65"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 36 + 12?",
    options: ["85", "71", "48", "11"],
    answer: "48"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 17 + 66?",
    options: ["18", "60", "83", "42"],
    answer: "83"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 30 + 66?",
    options: ["95", "28", "96", "17"],
    answer: "96"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 57 + 26?",
    options: ["83", "17", "31", "66"],
    answer: "83"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 10 + 40?",
    options: ["79", "47", "50", "26"],
    answer: "50"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 23 + 50?",
    options: ["37", "73", "16", "44"],
    answer: "73"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 11 + 45?",
    options: ["56", "36", "90", "21"],
    answer: "56"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 11 + 68?",
    options: ["15", "33", "84", "79"],
    answer: "79"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 22 + 57?",
    options: ["25", "27", "83", "79"],
    answer: "79"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 20 + 41?",
    options: ["99", "61", "65", "59"],
    answer: "61"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 41 + 46?",
    options: ["88", "46", "43", "87"],
    answer: "87"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 51 + 10?",
    options: ["61", "56", "81", "57"],
    answer: "61"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 12 + 79?",
    options: ["57", "65", "91", "90"],
    answer: "91"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 10 + 51?",
    options: ["20", "61", "24", "59"],
    answer: "61"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 57 + 24?",
    options: ["38", "23", "56", "81"],
    answer: "81"
  },
  {
    question: "What is 28 + 63?",
    options: ["25", "91", "54", "90"],
    answer: "91"
  },
];

export default level11questions;